

TIJANA GVOZDIC

PROFILE

UI/UX DESIGNER SOCIOLOGIST AND SWING DANCE TEACHER

I believe in practical design that combines creativity and solutions.

I'm taking my first steps in UI design with strong interest in process of user experience. I had learned coding for better understanding of web products and design possibilities.

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH - B2 LEVEL (IELTS)

SPANISH - B1 LEVEL

INTRESTS

SOCIAL HISTORY
VINTAGE FASHION
DIY AND CRAFTS
JAZZ HISTORY & DANCE
MUSIC, PLAYING DRUMMS

EDUCATION

BACHELOR WITH HONORS IN SOCIOLOGY FACULTY OF PHILOSOPHY, UNIVERSITY OF BELGRADE, AVERAGE SCORE 8.10

HIGH SCHOOL "GIMNAZIJA SVILAJNAC"
GENERAL STUDIES

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

BECOME A UX DESIGNER FROM SCRATCH INTERACTION DESIGN FONDATION

USER RESEARCH: METHODS AND BEST PRACTICES INTERACTION DESIGN FONDATION

DESIGN RULES: PRINCIPLES AND PRACTICES FOR GREAT UI DESIGN

JOE NATOLY, UDEMY ONLINE COURSES

MODERN HTML & CSS FROM THE BEGINNING (INCLUDING SASS)

BRAD TRAVERSY, UDEMY ONLINE COURSES

INTRODUCTION TO WEB

CODE SCHOOL BELGRADE, APRIL - JUN 2019.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP
ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR
FIGMA
ADOBE XD
HTML5 & CSS3
RESEARCH
DESIGN THINKING

SOFT

EMPATHY
ATTENTION TO DETAILS
PATIENCE
TEAM WORK AND COLLABORATION

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX DESIGNER - INTERNSHIP
"30 HILLS" BELGRADE
JUNE - SEPTEMBER 2021

ORGANIZER AND PROJECT MANAGER
"BELGRADE LINDY EXCHANGE FESTIVAL"
AUGUST 2015 - 2021

SWING DANCE INSTRUCTOR
2015 - 2021
CUSTOMER SUPPORT
"BIRDSEYE SOLUTIONS"
OKTOBER 2014 - NOVEMBER 2015

BARTENDER
"THE BLACK TURTLE PUB"
AUGUST 2013 - OKTOBER 2014
"BISTRO PASTIS"
MARCH - SEPTEMBER 2008

FREELANCE CONTRIBUTOR
"PARTENON" PUBLISHING COMPANY
2005

CONTACT

tijanagvozdic.tkgv@gmail.com +356 77 11 1389 +381 60 360 60 17